greensock.com 2016-11-06

# GreenSock | Privacy Policy

#### Version: 1.19.0 updated 2016-07-18

  *   * ###  github 

## CDN Link

Copy/paste this code into your HTML:

    <script src="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/gsap/1.19.0/TweenMax.min.js"></script>

  * Robust
  * Lightweight
  * Customize
  * Version: 

By using GreenSock code, you agree to the terms of use.

This privacy policy describes how GreenSock uses and protects any information that you provide on greensock.com. GreenSock is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. GreenSock may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. This policy is effective from May 2014.

**What we collect**  
We may collect the following information:

  * name and job title
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**What we do with the information we gather**  
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

**Internal record keeping.**

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided (you may opt out anytime).
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail.
  * We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
  * We may provide your information to our third party partners for marketing or promotional purposes.
  * We will never sell your information.

**Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**  
A cookie is a small file that is placed on your computer's hard drive by the web browser. It helps analyze web traffic and allows us to customize our site for you (like logging in to get your downloads or transaction receipts, etc.).

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes.

A cookie does not grant us access to your computer itself or any control thereof. 

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Links to other websites**  
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**  
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

You may change your email and account preferences by logging into your account at http://www.greensock.com/account/ or you may email us a request directly at info@greensock.com.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you change your email preferences accordingly (again, log in to http://www.greensock.com/account/ to do that).

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email info@greensock.com.

If you believe that any information we are holding about you is incorrect or incomplete, email us as soon as possible at info@greensock.com. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
